<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Website Footprint</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/</link><description>Recent content on Website Footprint</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://webfoot.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>InkTalks</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/inktalks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/inktalks/</guid><description>&lt;p>INK is India’s foremost platform for the exchange of cutting-edge ideas and inspiring stories. Known for the annual INK Conference, INK Asia, INK Salons, and programs such as INK Fellows, we are a community that accelerates the journeys of the game changers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>HikingProject</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/hikingproject/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/hikingproject/</guid><description>&lt;p>HikingProject is a crowd-sourced hiking guide built by hikers like you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Vingle</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/vingle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/vingle/</guid><description>&lt;p>Vingle is the social networking website. The social network was initially based on a South Korean website, but in 2014 moved to an iOS and Android app.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Gendou</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/gendou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/gendou/</guid><description>&lt;p>Gendou is an anime music database web application forum. Gendou is an big forum who allow people to talk, share and build community about anime and music.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SonicSquirrel</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/sonicsquirrel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/sonicsquirrel/</guid><description>&lt;p>SonicSquirrel is a platform and distribution channel for netlabels. its aim is to promote free music and help artists and netlabels make their work easily available for a wider audience. SonicSquirrel is not only about providing music, but also about giving background information and sensitizing people for issues like copyleft/right, drm and netaudio.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bitchute</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/bitchute/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/bitchute/</guid><description>&lt;p>BitChute is a peer-to-peer content sharing platform and associated services. BitChute aims to put creators first and provide them with a service that they can use to flourish and express their ideas freely.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Zeef</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/zeef/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/zeef/</guid><description>&lt;p>Curated Directory for Development &amp;amp; Tech Resources. Find 5.3M links hand-picked by 1,641 curators over 2,715 ZEEF pages.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OpenLearning</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/openlearning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/openlearning/</guid><description>&lt;p>Online learning like you’ve never experienced before. Empower yourself with world-class courses from educators and institutions in a practical and social learning environment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mifare</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/mifare/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/mifare/</guid><description>&lt;p>MIFARE® is NXP’s well-known brand for a wide range of contactless IC products with a typical read/write distance of 10 cm (4 inches) used in more than 40 different applications worldwide.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>DailyGram</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/dailygram/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/dailygram/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dailygram is the one and only business network, where thousands of new products and services are listed everyday. Share files, photos, and videos. Connect with potential new customers and suppliers. Best of all, it's free!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GuildWork</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/guildwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/guildwork/</guid><description>&lt;p>Build customized guild sites with HTML/CSS and create custom widgets using JavaScript.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Changemakers</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/changemakers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/changemakers/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ashoka Changemakers Challenges are competitions designed to connect innovative participants to one another to scale their impact. Add your idea to a Changemakers Challenge to get feedback, browse other entries, and join a powerful community of changemakers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GitBook</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/gitbook/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/gitbook/</guid><description>&lt;p>Document Everything! Write a what the Best practices, Thought and Ideas for you, your users and your team.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Neocities</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/neocities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/neocities/</guid><description>&lt;p>Create your own free website. Unlimited creativity, zero ads.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Neocities is a social network of 347,700 web sites that are bringing back the lost individual creativity of the web. We offer free static web hosting and tools that allow you to create your own web site. Join us!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Site123</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/site123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/site123/</guid><description>&lt;p>Create a free website with our content management system and establish your online presence. Share your website on social media and build a website today!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PBWorks</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbworks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbworks/</guid><description>&lt;p>Capture knowledge, share files, and manage projects within a secure, reliable environment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Telegraph</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/telegraph/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/telegraph/</guid><description>&lt;p>Telegra.ph is a minimalist publishing tool that allows you to create richly formatted posts and push them to the Web in just a click. Telegraph posts also get beautiful Instant View pages on Telegram.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Turnkeylinux</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/turnkeylinux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/turnkeylinux/</guid><description>&lt;p>Turnkey GNU/Linux is a free Debian based library of system images that pre-integrates and polishes the best free software components into secure, easy to use solutions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Weezevent</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/weezevent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/weezevent/</guid><description>&lt;p>All the features you need to easily organise an event in your image: online ticketing, registration management, invitations, and access control.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Ello</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/ello/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/ello/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ello is a global community of artists dedicated to creative excellence. Built by artists, for artists.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>BitLy</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/bitly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/bitly/</guid><description>&lt;p>A URL shortener built with powerful tools to help you grow and protect your brand. Bitly helps businesses shine by transforming their links into powerful tools for marketers and customer support teams.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Amsterdam Smart City</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/amsterdam-smart-city/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/amsterdam-smart-city/</guid><description>&lt;p>A world in transition requires an independent place where change makers can meet, interact and start working together. Amsterdam Smart City is that open and safe space for innovation and cooperation. We bring together innovative companies, knowledge institutions, public authorities and proactive citizens to shape the city of the future. We are a platform for doers. In this way we ensure better streets, neighbourhoods and cities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Opportunity</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/opportunity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/opportunity/</guid><description>&lt;p>MyOpportunity.com is here to help by taking care of the search for you. The secret sauce lies within our advanced lead matching algorithms that connect users from our 5,000,000+ network to opportunities based on variables that identify ‘who needs who or what’ anywhere in the world at anytime. Results are reported in real-time so members can take immediate action.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dreamwidth</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/dreamwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/dreamwidth/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dreamwidth Studios is a home and a community for all kinds of creative folk. Share your writing, your artwork, or your innermost thoughts. Find others who create the sort of things you like to enjoy. Control who can see your creation with our fine-grained privacy controls. Participate in communities for any one of a hundred topics. We are an independent, Open Source, community-centric service, and we support diversity in all its forms. Come dream with us.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PBase</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbase/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbase/</guid><description>&lt;p>PBase will host and share your photos on the Internet. If you are new to PBase, get started by viewing some of the millions of photos uploaded by our users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GitHub</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/github/</guid><description>&lt;p>GitHub, Inc. is a provider of Internet hosting for software development and version control using Git. It offers the distributed version control and source code management (SCM) functionality of Git, plus its own features. It provides access control and several collaboration features such as bug tracking, feature requests, task management, continuous integration and wikis for every project. Headquartered in California, it has been a subsidiary of Microsoft since 2018.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Read The Docs</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/read-the-docs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/read-the-docs/</guid><description>&lt;p>Read the Docs is software documentation by automating building, versioning, and hosting of your docs for you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Micro Blog</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/micro-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/micro-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p>micro.blog is a microblogging and social networking service created by Manton Reece, the first large multi-user social media service to support the Webmention and Micropub standards published by the World Wide Web Consortium.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Microsoft Social</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/microsoft-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/microsoft-social/</guid><description>&lt;p>Microsoft Social is the social network platform created by Microsoft Corporation. To get the most out of Microsoft we believe that you should sign in and become a member. It's free and by doing so you gain immediate access to interacting on the forums, sharing code samples, publishing articles and commenting on blog posts.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>MojoMarketPlace</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/mojomarket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/mojomarket/</guid><description>&lt;p>MOJO Marketplace is a community of web professionals providing digital goods and services that empower you to Build a Better Website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Gumroad</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/gumroad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/gumroad/</guid><description>&lt;p>Gumroad is an online platform that facilitates the sale of products by creators directly to consumers. Sahil Lavingia founded the company in 2011 with the intention of making selling as easy as social sharing. Although Lavingia claimed &amp;ldquo;I don’t think five years ago this could have existed&amp;rdquo;, there have been companies with a similar purpose since 2004, such as PayLoadz, E-junkie, and TradeBit. The company received more than $8 million in funding. Within three years Gumroad had to lay-off most of its staff to stay afloat. Founder Sahil Lavingia in 2010&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OpenDrive</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/opendrive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/opendrive/</guid><description>&lt;p>OpenDRIVE files are designed to describe entire road networks with respect to all data belonging to the road environment. They do not describe the entities acting on or interacting with the road. The OpenDRIVE data is made available to e.g. Vehicle Dynamics and Traffic Simulation via a layer of routines for the evaluation of the information contained in the OpenDRIVE file.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Reddit</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/reddit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/reddit/</guid><description>&lt;p>Reddit is a website comprising user-generated content—including photos, videos, links, and text-based posts—and discussions of this content in what is essentially a bulletin board system. The name &amp;ldquo;Reddit&amp;rdquo; is a play-on-words with the phrase &amp;ldquo;read it&amp;rdquo;, i.e., &amp;ldquo;I read it on Reddit.&amp;rdquo; According to Reddit, in 2019 there were approximately 430 million monthly users, who are known as &amp;ldquo;redditors&amp;rdquo;. The site's content is divided into categories or communities known on-site as &amp;ldquo;subreddits&amp;rdquo;, of which there are more than 138,000 active communities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/contact/</guid><description>Have any questions? Just feel free to contact us.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/about/</guid><description>WebFoot is about we are traveling to all big websites for learn, tester and review.</description></item></channel></rss>