<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>80++ on Website Footprint</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/tags/80++/</link><description>Recent content in 80++ on Website Footprint</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://webfoot.netlify.app/tags/80++/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bitchute</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/bitchute/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/bitchute/</guid><description>&lt;p>BitChute is a peer-to-peer content sharing platform and associated services. BitChute aims to put creators first and provide them with a service that they can use to flourish and express their ideas freely.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Neocities</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/neocities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/neocities/</guid><description>&lt;p>Create your own free website. Unlimited creativity, zero ads.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Neocities is a social network of 347,700 web sites that are bringing back the lost individual creativity of the web. We offer free static web hosting and tools that allow you to create your own web site. Join us!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Site123</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/site123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/site123/</guid><description>&lt;p>Create a free website with our content management system and establish your online presence. Share your website on social media and build a website today!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PBWorks</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbworks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbworks/</guid><description>&lt;p>Capture knowledge, share files, and manage projects within a secure, reliable environment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Weezevent</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/weezevent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/weezevent/</guid><description>&lt;p>All the features you need to easily organise an event in your image: online ticketing, registration management, invitations, and access control.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dreamwidth</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/dreamwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/dreamwidth/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dreamwidth Studios is a home and a community for all kinds of creative folk. Share your writing, your artwork, or your innermost thoughts. Find others who create the sort of things you like to enjoy. Control who can see your creation with our fine-grained privacy controls. Participate in communities for any one of a hundred topics. We are an independent, Open Source, community-centric service, and we support diversity in all its forms. Come dream with us.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PBase</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbase/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/pbase/</guid><description>&lt;p>PBase will host and share your photos on the Internet. If you are new to PBase, get started by viewing some of the millions of photos uploaded by our users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>MojoMarketPlace</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/mojomarket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/mojomarket/</guid><description>&lt;p>MOJO Marketplace is a community of web professionals providing digital goods and services that empower you to Build a Better Website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OpenDrive</title><link>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/opendrive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://webfoot.netlify.app/post/opendrive/</guid><description>&lt;p>OpenDRIVE files are designed to describe entire road networks with respect to all data belonging to the road environment. They do not describe the entities acting on or interacting with the road. The OpenDRIVE data is made available to e.g. Vehicle Dynamics and Traffic Simulation via a layer of routines for the evaluation of the information contained in the OpenDRIVE file.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>